Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Walter H. Stainton
    - Correspondence with Museum of Modern Art regarding films, 1950-1955 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - New York State Plays Project, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Willard Straight Theater improvements and upkeep, 1944-1952 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Inventory, 1946-1956 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Narcissus dance choreography, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Pied Piper of Hamelintown and Narcissus dance notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous publications and clippings, 1922-1927 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Typescripts of Civil War letters, 1862-1864 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - George McCalmon
    - Donations and gifts, 1953-1962 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - American National Theatre and Academy publications, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA), 1957-1964 (Box 19, Folder 42-43)
    - ANTA International Cultural Exchange Service correspondence - tour, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - National Theatre Assembly, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Requests for plays, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - University Theatre Executive Board minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - McCalmon correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 19, Folder 48-49)
    - Film policies, 1955, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Ithaca Community Players, 1949-1955 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts XII, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts XIII, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts XIV, 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts XVI-XVIII, 1961-1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Festival of Contemporary Arts booklets, 1945-1946, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Announcements to theatre magazines, 1955-1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Theater financial reports, 1952-1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Scheduling Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Thesis on Central Staging, J. Burian, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Audio-visual, catalogs, misc., 1956-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Report of the Director of Summer Session, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - BEAN-O Dramatic Club banquet, 1954-1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - University Theater Certificate of Compliance, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Drummond Playwriting Contest, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 12-16)
    - Cornell Dance Club, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan - Savoyards, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous interdepartmental correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Cornell United Religious Work, 1954-1962 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Faculty minutes and reports, 1955-1963 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - New York State Community Theatre correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - New York State Community Theatre bulletins and minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
    - History of the University Theatre and Dramatic Club, 1909-1952 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Daily Sun and Alumni News clippings, 1922-1951 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - "Traffic Signals" by A.M. Drummond [memorabilia, script, photos], 1926-1950 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Inventory of CDC scrapbooks, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Kermit Hunter correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Constance Kuhn, "Revolution in the Theatre", 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - CDC correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Heermans Prize, 1953-1956 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Willard Straight Hall correspondence, 1945-1954 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - McCalmon correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Studio reports and correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Publicity and Correspondence
    - Publicity, 1952-1953, 1959-1966 (Box 23, Folder 47-54)
    - Publicity, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
    - Summer Theatre publicity and correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 26, Folder 4-10)
    - Summer Theatre staff, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
      [contains photographs]
    - An Evening of One Act Plays (Champeen of the Canawl; Portrait of a Madonna; The Cocklepfiefer Case), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - A Program of One-Act Plays (Village Wooing; A Matter of Husbands; Fumed Oak), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - A Program of One-Act Plays (At Liberty; Love and How to Cure It; I'm a Fool; Pyramus and Thisbe), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - A Program of One-Act Plays (The Hope Chest; Materia Medica; Murder is Fun!), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Plays of Three Nations (Sunday Costs Five Pesos; Evening Dress Indispensable; Hello Out There), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Three One-Act Plays (Murder is Fun!; Evening Dress Indispensable; Hello Out There), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Four One-Act Plays (How He Lied to Her Husband; Mild Oats; Such Things Only Happen in Books; Quiet-Facing the Park), 1944 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Five One-Act Plays (Little Immortal; Overtones; The Power of Fate; Sparkin'; The Square Triangle), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Four One-Act Plays (Some Women Were Talking; The Bridegroom Waits; The Odd Streak; Lonesome-Like), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Four One-Act Plays (Hello Out There; All on a Summer's Day; Mild Oats; The Power of Fate), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Four One-Act Plays (Hat and Stick; Some Women were Talking; Everybody's Husband; The Pot Boiler), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Three One-Act Period Plays (Box and Cox, Married and Settled; The Choir Rehearsal; Exile), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Ivan [film presentation], 1947 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Jero Magon's Marionettes - Arabian Nights: Aladdin and his Wonderful Lamp; Marco Millions, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Jim Dandy, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - The Baker's Wife [film presentation], 1941 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - The Good Earth [film]; Red Gate Players [Chinese shadow plays], 1948 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Hay Fever, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Henry V [film], 1948 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Holy Matrimony [film], 1945 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - How Green was my Valley [film], 1945 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - In Which We Serve [film], 1944 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner [film], 1943 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Maedchen in Uniform [film], 1945 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Ladies in Retirement, 1941, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - The Lost Weekend [film], 1947 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Alan Lomax and Leadbelly [live performance], 1947 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - The Lives of a Bengal Lancer [film], 1945 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Lifeboat [film], 1946 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Million Dollar Legs [film], 1946 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Heermans Prize Plays, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - The Ascent of F6, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - As You Like It, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - The Bonds of Interest, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Boy Meets Girl, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - A Child is Born, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Joan of Lorraine, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - The Last Chance [film], 1948 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Milestones, circa 1931 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Kind Lady, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Angel Street, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Arms and the Man, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Heart of Paris [film], 1946 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Headin' for Havana, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Four One-Act Plays (Fumed Oak; They Refuse to be Resurrected; Etiquette; A Pound on Demand), 1946 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - One-Act Plays (Shall We Join the Ladies?; Travelling Light; Fancy Free; The Choir Rehearsal), 1946 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Cornell One-Act Plays (A Man Should Have a Wife; (Unnamed); Three Cheers for Woody), 1950 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Deep are the Roots, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Three One-Act Plays (Pullman Car Hiawatha; Idyl on a Summer Hotel Porch; Two Gentleman of Soho), 1946 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning; Hands Across the Sea, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - The Barretts of Wimpole Street, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - John Gabriel Borkman, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Tatterman Marionettes, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Stone Flower, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Springtime for Henry, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Specter of the Rose (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Shoe Shine (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - The Seventh Veil (film), 1947 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - The Second Shepherd's Play, 1946-1948 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Three One-Act Plays (The General Retreats; Bath at Cayuga Bridge; Aria Da Capo), 1949 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - An Evening of One Act Plays (That's Hollywood; Papa Never Done Nothing... Much; Mooney's Kid Don't Cry; They Refuse to Be Resurrected), 1949 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Of Mice and Men, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Dr. Knock, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Angna Enters (dance performance), 1947, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - The Second Man, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - The Music Hall Show, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - An Inspector Calls, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - The Play's the Thing, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - HMS Pinafore, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - Cornell One-Act Plays, 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Children of Paradise (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Crossfire (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - The Damask Cheek, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - Dead of Night (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - Special Anniversary Film Program, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 81)
    - Camille (film), 1946 (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - The Captive Heart (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 84)
    - Charlie Chaplin Film Festival, 1946-1947 (Box 53, Folder 85)
    - Newspaper clippings, Cornell theater performances, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 86)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 87)
    - Bombshell (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 88)
    - Brief Music, 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 89)
    - Across the Continent, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 90)
    - Ah, Wilderness!, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 91)
    - Alison's House, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 92)
    - The Ghost Goes West (film), 1948 (Box 53, Folder 93)
    - Fantasia (film), 1947-1948 (Box 53, Folder 94)
    - Fanny's First Play, 1930, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 95)
      [contains photographs, 1930]
    - Mr. Pim Passes By, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 96)
    - Home and Beauty, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 97)
    - Morning's at Seven, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 98)
    - They Knew What They Wanted, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 99)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 100)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 101)
    - Two Blind Mice, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 102)
    - Trial by Jury, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 103)
    - The Vinegar Tree, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 104)
    - The Wild Duck, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 105)
    - The Winslow Boy, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 106)
    - The Little Foxes, 1943, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 107)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 108)
    - The Male Animal, 1941, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 109)
    - The Mikado, 1951-1952 (Box 53, Folder 110)
    - The Beautiful People, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 111)
    - The Beachcomber, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 112)
    - Beau Brummel (film), 1945 (Box 53, Folder 113)
    - Beyond the Horizon, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 114)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 115)
    - The Doctor in Spite of Himself, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 116)
    - Happy Birthday, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 117)
    - Production by the Kermis Club, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 118)
    - An Evening of One Act Plays (November 21-22) - correspondence, publicity, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - An Evening of One Act Plays (May 7-8) - correspondence, publicity, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Night Must Fall - correspondence, publicity, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - An Evening of One Act Plays (July 30-31) - correspondence, publicity, Summer 1948 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - You Touched Me! - correspondence, publicity, October 1948 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - MacBeth - correspondence and press releases, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Once Upon a Hill - correspondence, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Pyramus and Thisbe - correspondence, production notes, 1950-1962 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest - correspondence and press releases, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - The Detour - press releases, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - The Vegetable - correspondence and publicity, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Cornell One-Act Plays (The Late Adam Fry; The Big Cheese; The Fishbowl) - correspondence, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - On the High Road - publicity, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Romeo and Juliet - correspondence and publicity, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Desire Under the Elms - correspondence, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - The Pirates of Penzance - correspondence, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - The Family Reunion - correspondence and publicity, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Awake and Sing! - correspondence, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Tambou - correspondence, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Ten Nights in a Bar-Room - correspondence and publicity, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Hay Fever - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Juno and the Paycock - correspondence, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Patience - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - The Autumn Garden - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - The Tempest - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - The Country Wife - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - The Glass Menagerie - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - The Christmas Invasion - correspondence and publicity, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - The Lady's Not for Burning - correspondence and publicity, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Hedda Gabler - correspondence and publicity, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Twelfth Night - correspondence and publicity, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Blood Wedding - publicity, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - The Pursuit of Happiness - correspondence and publicity, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Right You Are - publicity, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors - correspondence and publicity, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Electra - correspondence and publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - The Flowering Peach - correspondence and publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - The Would-Be Invalid (Le Malade Imaginaire) - publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Misalliance - correspondence and publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - All Summer Long - correspondence and publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Bernardine - correspondence and publicity, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Once Upon a Hill - Founder's Day program and articles, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan - correspondence and publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - The Witchfinders - correspondence and publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Favor Island - publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Papa is All - correspondence and publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - The Tavern - publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors - correspondence and publicity, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Studio '58 publicity, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Othello - publicity, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Shadow and Substance - correspondence, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - A Different Drummer - correspondence and publicity, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - The Haunted House - correspondence and publicity, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Bell, Book and Candle - correspondence and publicity, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - The Rivals - publicity, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Antigone - publicity, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Ghosts - publicity and production information, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Under Milkwood - publicity, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Taming of the Shrew - publicity, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - My Three Angels - publicity, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - The Boy Friend - publicity, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Studio '60 publicity, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Death of a Salesman - publicity, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Dr. Faustus - publicity, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Twilight Bar - publicity, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Thieves' Carnival - publicity, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Pictures in the Hallway - publicity, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Three Russian Comedies (Gamblers; A Marriage Proposal; Squaring the Circle) - correspondence and publicity, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Volpone - publicity, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - The Time of Your Life - publicity, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - The Great God Brown - publicity and box office reports, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - The Gondoliers - publicity and box office reports, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Three Way Split (The Sandbox; The Room; The Future is in Eggs) - publicity and box office reports, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Man and Superman - publicity, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Oedipus the King - publicity, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - As You Like It - correspondence and publicity, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - The Fantasticks - correspondence, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Lysistrata - correspondence and production notes, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Rosmersholm - correspondence, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Look Back in Anger - correspondence and publicity, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Finnegans Wake - correspondence and publicity, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - The Jew of Malta - correspondence and publicity, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - The Happy Haven - correspondence, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Tartuffe - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - The Great Magician - correspondence and publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof - correspondence and publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Telemachus Clay - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - All the King's Men - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - The Devil in America - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Ah, Wilderness! - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - The Man of Mode - publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - The Physicists - correspondence and publicity, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Medusa - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Uncle Vanya - correspondence and publicity, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Three Modern Plays (Act Without Words I; The Difficult Hour III; The Bald Soprano) - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Saint Joan of the Stockyards - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - The Knack - correspondence and publicity, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - The Hostage - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - The Gambler - correspondence, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - The Knack - correspondence and publicity, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - King Richard III - study guide and publicity, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Dracula - study guide and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Andorra - correspondence, study guide and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - The Threepenny Opera - correspondence, study guide and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - The Deadly Game - correspondence, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - A Taste of Honey - correspondence and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - The Cave Dwellers - correspondence and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - The Blood Knot - publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - The Egg - correspondence and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Barthol'mew Fair - publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Getting Married - study guide and publicity, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Mary Stuart - correspondence, study guide and publicity, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Zoo - correspondence and publicity, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Orontea - correspondence, libretto and publicity, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - The Acharnians - correspondence and publicity, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - The School for Wives - correspondence and publicity, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - The Rules of the Game - correspondence and publicity, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Scripts and Prompt Books
    - Jess of the Bar Z Ranch by Forbes Heermans, 1902 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Under the Oaks by E. L. Laporte; Simple Honors by Elizabeth Goepp and Constance Connor Brown; Ashes of Sweets by George Fass; Three Pasos of Lope de Rueda by W.C. Capune, W.H. French, and J.N. Williams; Gamaliel the High Priest (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Cophetua's Queen by Julian M. Drachman; The Announcement by I.T.C. Dissinger; As Far As I Know by K.R. Wallace; The Trouble in the Bubble by Sidney S. Kingsley (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - The Magic Called Love by Sidney S. Kirshner; Untitled; Friends by D.E. Keenan (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - 619. Portrait of Polish Family by Lloyd Weninger (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - The Glass Menagerie - Author: Tennessee Williams, 1953?; Prompt book (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Kagekiyo - Author: Seami Motokiyo - Director: Brian Meeson (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - The Shoemaker's House, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Corner of God by Louis Adelman, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Sea-Wife by Maxwell Anderson, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - In Noah's Ark by Rumer Godden, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - The Unknown Woman from Arras by Armand Salacrou, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Like Falling Leaves (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Jim Dandy by William Saroyan, undated; (script and music) (Box 38)
    - Dagzil by James V. Hatch, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - The Four Sons of Aymon by Herman Closson, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - This is My Valley by Dorothy R. Stewart, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Doctor for a Dumb Wife by F. Duerr, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - A Fake is a Fake by Friedrich von Bachlein, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - The Family Romance by June Dudley Donnell, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Henry and the Mimzies by Joanna Russ, 1955; (script and notes) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Jade Bracelet by Fairfax Proudfit Walkup and De Witt Bodeen, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Saturday Stranger by Joseph Rosenberg, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Lo, The Angel by Nancy Wallace, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Full Score by Theodore Hatlen, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - A Power of Dreams by Peter John Stephens, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - The Day of a Faun by Archie Binns, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - The Inconstant Moon by Irving Kreutz, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Mary and Her Sergeant by Wm. Philip Smith, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - They Got Every Night by Fred Myers, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Lefty Peroni by Georgia Backus, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Repayment by Ralph Brewster, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - The Blind Shall See by John Fleming, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - The Devil to Pay by Brian Dillon, undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - The Doctor and the Devils by Dylan Thomas, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Supernaturally Speaking by John Fleming, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - The Wonder Worker of the Plains by Sandra Goldberg, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)